Hello friends, welcome to the Investment Information
YouTube channel. In
today's video, we will
talk about a total of seven companies that have
announced a stock split along with a dividend
and have
also fixed a record date for giving that dividend. First of all, let's
look at KPI Green Energy
Limited. When I am shooting this video, the
share price of this company
is
Rs. 1875 and the market capitalization of this company
is more than Rs. 11 crore. The
52 week high of this company is
Rs. 210915 and the 52 week low of this company
is
Rs. 323. KPI Green Energy Limited has
announced a stock split in the ratio of 1:2, which means that one share will become two
shares, which means that the number of shares will
double. Now let's talk
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Limited. When I am shooting this video, the
share price of this company is
Rs. 1650 40 and this  The company has a market
capitalization of more than Rs 82 thousand crores
and the 52 week high of this company
is
Rs 1747 and the 52 week low of this company
Rs 16630. ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company Limited has announced a
final dividend of Rs 6
and the company has
set a record date to pay it on June 7,
2024. Now let's talk about Alkyl Mines
Chemicals Limited. When I am
shooting this video, the
share price of this company is
₹19540 and the market capitalization of this company is
around Rs 10000 crores
and the 52 week high of this company is
and the 52 week low of this company is
Rs 1808. Alkyl
Amines Chemicals Limited has announced a final dividend of Rs 10 and the record date to pay it on
June 25.
2024 Let's talk
about Precision Camshaft Limited. When I am
shooting this video, the
share price of this company is
Rs 19145 and the market capitalization of this company
is around Rs 2000 crore
and the 52 week high of this company is
Rs 319 and the 52 week low of this company is
Rs 149 35. Precision Camshaft
Limited has announced a final dividend of one rupee
and the
company has set a record date for giving it on July 19,
2024. Let's talk about Concord Biotech
Limited. When I am shooting this video, the
share price of this company
is
Rs 144 and the market capitalization of this company
is more than Rs 15000 crore
and the 52 week high of this company
is
Rs 1725 and the 52 week low of this company is
Rs 9005. Concord Biotech Limited has made a profit of
Rs 875 which is a quarter.  A final dividend of nine rupees has been
announced and
the company has set a record date of
22 June
2024 to pay it. Let's talk
about Exchange Solutions Limited. When I am
shooting this video, the
share price of this company is 118
65 rupees and the market
capitalization of this company is more than 1000 crore rupees
and the 52 week high of this company is
rupees and the 52 week low of this company
is 6030
rupees. Exchange Solutions
Limited has announced a final dividend of four rupees including a
special
dividend of two rupees and the
record date of 14 June
2024 to pay it. Let's talk about Well Jan Dennison
Limited. When I am shooting this video, the
share price of this company
is 379
rupees and the market capitalization of this company
is around
850 crore rupees.  And the 52 week high of this company
is
Rs 391490 and the 52 week low of this company is
Rs 61502. Welljan Dennison Limited has
announced a final dividend of Rs 17.
So friends, if you liked this video, then
like this video and
subscribe to the channel.